{
    "id": "bcd55d2aabd243dbbc9fab6914855953",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was let off …………………. he would not repeat the offence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "on condition that",
                "in order that",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "616bd7196b5449e9945e2755bb43ab15"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wore a coat ………………… he might not catch cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in order that",
                "provided that",
                "on condition that",
                "so as to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ac2d44f0f9914b8699866fdfafc53fbb"
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been raining continuously ………………….. yesterday morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "from",
                "since",
                "ago"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "efe24192afbf48cd9ef3551d1634ad32"
        },
        {
            "question": "The conference will take place between the 10th …………………. the 16th of June.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "through",
                "to",
                "None of these"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f6c793db4ec7444bb2373ec1e931221d"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the kind of music that I like to listen .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "from",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bea1adf73aaa434c85d1a63bb67b6715"
        },
        {
            "question": "Here is the man that I was talking to you …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "about",
                "with",
                "None of these"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "12a2f7a5d37346ba9777592b0b3d66c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. my best efforts, I could not win the election.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "By means",
                "Owing to",
                "In spite of",
                "On behalf of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e1a20bab5f5043299f3badd8fe5048f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Pay your fee on time lest you ……………….. be fined.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "could",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6557658aac1f4b5cafd133f1e5e30da9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. only say what he wants and it will be granted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need",
                "would",
                "could",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "625fc3f5f81b4f6dbcf745952902671a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know if we can fully confide ..................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "at",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dcff7f8e73aa40cd87c00fc3fd8a9eff"
        }
    ]
}